Women's Bookstore collection
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Publications, 1969 - 1997; F-111-8; 2.3 m of textual records 212 newspapers
  - Kinesis, 1974 - 1986; F-111-8-0-0-39 (Newspaper box 111-28)
    - Kinesis, October 1982; F-111-8-0-0-39-71
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item87.
    - Kinesis, June 1985; F-111-8-0-0-39-72
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item88.
    - Kinesis, July 1985 - August 1985; F-111-8-0-0-39-73
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item89.
    - Kinesis, September 1985; F-111-8-0-0-39-74
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item90.
    - Kinesis, October 1985; F-111-8-0-0-39-75
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item91.
    - Kinesis, February 1986; F-111-8-0-0-39-76
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item92.
    - Kinesis, May 1987; F-111-8-0-0-39-77
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-item93.
  - Labour Challenge, 1971 - 1974; F-111-8-0-0-40 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Lavender Woman, 1974 - 1975; F-111-8-0-0-41 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - leftwords, 1979 - 1983; F-111-8-0-0-42 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Lesbian Connection, 1977 - 1981; F-111-8-0-0-43 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Lilith, 1977 - 1981; F-111-8-0-0-44 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Long Time Coming, 1973 - 1974; F-111-8-0-0-45 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - des luttes et des rires, 1980 - 1982; F-111-8-0-0-46 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Majority Report, 1973 - 1977; F-111-8-0-0-47 (Newspaper box 111-31)
    - Majority Report, vol. 3 no. 3, July 1973; F-111-8-0-0-47-1
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item94.
    - Majority Report, vol. 4 no. 3, May 1974; F-111-8-0-0-47-2
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item95.
    - Majority Report, vol. 4 no. 8, August 1974; F-111-8-0-0-47-3
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item96.
    - Majority Report, vol. 4 no. 15, November 1974; F-111-8-0-0-47-4
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item97.
    - Majority Report, vol. 4 no. 18, January 1975; F-111-8-0-0-47-5
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item98.
    - Majority Report, vol. 4 no. 20, February 1975; F-111-8-0-0-47-6
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item99.
    - Majority Report, vol. 4 no. 21, February 1975; F-111-8-0-0-47-7
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item100.
    - Majority Report, vol. 4 no. 23, March 1975; F-111-8-0-0-47-8
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item101.
    - Majority Report, vol. 5 no. 3, June 1975; F-111-8-0-0-47-9
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item102.
    - Majority Report, vol. 5 no. 6, July 1975; F-111-8-0-0-47-10
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item103.
    - Majority Report, vol. 5 no. 16, December 1975; F-111-8-0-0-47-11
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item104.
    - Majority Report, vol. 5 no. 20, February 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-12
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item105.
    - Majority Report, vol. 5 no. 22, March 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-13
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item106.
    - Majority Report, vol. 5 no. 23, March 1976 - April 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-14
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item107.
    - Majority Report, vol. 5 no. 24, April 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-15
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item108.
    - Majority Report, vol. 5 no. 26, May 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-16
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item109.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 1, May 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-17
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item110.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 2, May 1976 - June 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-18
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item111.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 3, June 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-19
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item112.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 4, June 1976 - July 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-20
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item113.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 5, July 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-21
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item114.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 6, July 1976 - August 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-22
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item115.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 7, August 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-23
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item116.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 8, August 1976 - September 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-24
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item117.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 9, September 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-25
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item118.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 10, September 1976 - October 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-26
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item119.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 11, October 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-27
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item120.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 12, October 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-28
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item121.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 13, October 1976 - November 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-29
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item122.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 15, November 1976 - December 1976; F-111-8-0-0-47-30
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item123.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 18, January 1977; F-111-8-0-0-47-31
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item124.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 19, January 1977 - February 1977; F-111-8-0-0-47-32
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item125.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 20, February 1977; F-111-8-0-0-47-33
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item126.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 21, February 1977 - March 1977; F-111-8-0-0-47-34
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item127.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 22, March 1977; F-111-8-0-0-47-35
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item128.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 25, April 1977; F-111-8-0-0-47-36
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item129.
    - Majority Report, vol. 6 no. 26, April 1977 - May 1977; F-111-8-0-0-47-37
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item130.
    - Majority Report, vol. 7 no. 1, May 1977; F-111-8-0-0-47-38
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item131.
    - Majority Report, vol. 7 no. 2, May 1977 - June 1977; F-111-8-0-0-47-39
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item132.
    - Majority Report, vol. 7 no. 3, June 1977; F-111-8-0-0-47-40
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-47, F-111-item133.
  - The Manitoba Women's Newspaper, 1986; F-111-8-0-0-48 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Maternal Health News, [ca 1970] - [ca 1979]; F-111-8-0-0-49 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Media Report to Women, 1974 - 1975; F-111-8-0-0-50 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - The Menstrual Review, 1974 - 1975; F-111-8-0-0-51 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Momma, 1976; F-111-8-0-0-52 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Monitor, 1976; F-111-8-0-0-53 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - Moving Out, 1971 - 1972; F-111-8-0-0-54 (Urc tote box 111-22)
  - National Anti-Poverty Organization News, 1975; F-111-8-0-0-55 (Urc tote box 111-23)
  - The New Feminist, 1972 - 1973; F-111-8-0-0-56 (Urc tote box 111-23)
  - New Leaf, 1971 - 1972; F-111-8-0-0-57 (Urc tote box 111-23)
  - The New Woman Survival Catalog, 1973; F-111-8-0-0-58
  - No More Cages, 1981 - 1982; F-111-8-0-0-59 (Urc tote box 111-23)
  - The Northern Woman, 1975; F-111-8-0-0-60 (Urc tote box 111-23)
  - Northwest Passage, 1974 - 1982; F-111-8-0-0-61 (Urc tote box 111-23)
  - Now [National Organization of Women], 1970 - 1980; F-111-8-0-0-62 (Urc tote box 111-23)
  - Off Our Backs, 1970 - 1980; F-111-8-0-0-63 (Newspaper box 111-32)
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 1 no. 16, January 1970; F-111-8-0-0-63-1
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item134.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 1 no. 3, March 1970; F-111-8-0-0-63-2
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item135.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 1 no. 5, May 1970; F-111-8-0-0-63-3
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item136.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 1 no. 6, May 1970; F-111-8-0-0-63-4
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item137.
    - Off Our Backs, July 1970; F-111-8-0-0-63-5
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item138.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 1 no. 11, September 1970; F-111-8-0-0-63-6
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item139.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 1 no. 13, November 1970; F-111-8-0-0-63-7
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item140.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 1 no. 14, December 1970; F-111-8-0-0-63-8
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item141.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 1 no. 15, December 1970; F-111-8-0-0-63-9
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item142.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 1 no. 18, February 1971; F-111-8-0-0-63-10
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item143.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 1 no. 19, March 1971; F-111-8-0-0-63-11
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item144.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 1 no. 20, April 1971; F-111-8-0-0-63-12
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item145.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 1 no. 21, May 1971; F-111-8-0-0-63-13
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item146.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 1 no. 22, May 1971; F-111-8-0-0-63-14
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item147.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 1 no. 23, June 1971; F-111-8-0-0-63-15
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item148.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 1 no. 24, July 1971; F-111-8-0-0-63-16
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item149.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 2 no. 3, November 1971; F-111-8-0-0-63-17
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item150.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 2 no. 4, December 1971; F-111-8-0-0-63-18
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item151.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 2 no. 5, January 1972; F-111-8-0-0-63-19
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item152.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 2 no. 6, February 1972 - March 1972; F-111-8-0-0-63-20
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item153.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 2 no. 9, May 1972 - June 1972; F-111-8-0-0-63-21
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item154.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 3 no. 2, October 1972; F-111-8-0-0-63-22
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item155.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 3 no. 11, October 1973; F-111-8-0-0-63-23
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item156.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 3 no. 12, November 1973; F-111-8-0-0-63-24
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item157.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 4 no. 1, December 1973; F-111-8-0-0-63-25
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item158.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 4 no. 2, December 1973 - January 1974; F-111-8-0-0-63-26
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item159.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 4 no. 3, February 1974; F-111-8-0-0-63-27
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item160.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 4 no. 4, March 1974; F-111-8-0-0-63-28
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item161.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 4 no. 6, May 1974; F-111-8-0-0-63-29
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item162.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 4 no. 7, June 1974; F-111-8-0-0-63-30
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item163.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 4 no. 8, July 1974; F-111-8-0-0-63-31
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item164.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 4 no. 9, August 1974 - September 1974; F-111-8-0-0-63-32
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item165.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 4 no. 10, October 1974; F-111-8-0-0-63-33
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item166.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 4 no. 11, November 1974; F-111-8-0-0-63-34
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item167.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 4 no. 12, December 1974 - November 1974; F-111-8-0-0-63-35
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item168.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 5 no. 1, January 1975; F-111-8-0-0-63-36
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item169.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 5 no. 2, February 1975; F-111-8-0-0-63-37
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item170.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 5 no. 2, February 1975; F-111-8-0-0-63-38
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item171.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 5 no. 3, March 1975; F-111-8-0-0-63-39
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item172.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 5 no. 4, April 1975 - May 1975; F-111-8-0-0-63-40
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item173.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 5 no. 5, May 1975 - June 1975; F-111-8-0-0-63-41
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item174.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 5 no. 6, July 1975; F-111-8-0-0-63-42
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item175.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 5 no. 7, August 1975; F-111-8-0-0-63-43
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item176.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 5 no. 8, September 1975 - October 1975; F-111-8-0-0-63-44
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item177.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 5 no. 10, December 1975; F-111-8-0-0-63-45
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item178.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 5 no. 11, January 1976 - February 1976; F-111-8-0-0-63-46
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item179.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 6 no. 1, March 1976; F-111-8-0-0-63-47
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item180.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 6 no. 2, April 1976; F-111-8-0-0-63-48
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item181.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 6 no. 3, May 1976; F-111-8-0-0-63-49
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item182.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 6 no. 4, June 1976; F-111-8-0-0-63-50
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item183.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 6 no. 5, July 1976 - August 1976; F-111-8-0-0-63-51
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item184.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 7 no. 1, February 1977; F-111-8-0-0-63-52
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item185.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 7 no. 2, March 1977; F-111-8-0-0-63-53
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item186.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 7 no. 8, October 1977; F-111-8-0-0-63-54
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item187.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 7 no. 9, November 1977; F-111-8-0-0-63-55
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item188.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 8 no. 1, January 1978; F-111-8-0-0-63-56
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item189.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 8 no. 2, February 1978; F-111-8-0-0-63-57
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item190.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 8 no. 3, March 1978; F-111-8-0-0-63-58
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item191.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 8 no. 4, April 1978; F-111-8-0-0-63-59
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item192.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 8 no. 5, May 1978; F-111-8-0-0-63-60
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item193.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 8 no. 6, June 1978; F-111-8-0-0-63-61
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item194.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 8 no. 7, July 1978; F-111-8-0-0-63-62
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item195.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 8 no. 8, August 1978 - September 1978; F-111-8-0-0-63-63
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item196.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 8 no. 9, October 1978; F-111-8-0-0-63-64
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item197.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 8 no. 11, December 1978; F-111-8-0-0-63-65
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item198.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 9 no. 1, January 1979; F-111-8-0-0-63-66
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item199.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 9 no. 2, February 1979; F-111-8-0-0-63-67
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item200.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 9 no. 3, March 1979; F-111-8-0-0-63-68
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item201.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 9 no. 4, April 1979; F-111-8-0-0-63-69
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item202.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 9 no. 5, May 1979; F-111-8-0-0-63-70
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item203.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 9 no. 6, June 1979; F-111-8-0-0-63-71
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item204.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 9 no. 7, July 1979; F-111-8-0-0-63-72
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item205.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 9 no. 8, August 1979 - September 1979; F-111-8-0-0-63-73
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item206.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 9 no. 9, October 1979; F-111-8-0-0-63-74
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item207.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 9 no. 10, November 1979; F-111-8-0-0-63-75
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item208.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 9 no. 11, December 1979; F-111-8-0-0-63-76
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item209.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 10 no. 1, January 1980; F-111-8-0-0-63-77
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item210.
    - Off Our Backs, vol. 10 no. 4, April 1980; F-111-8-0-0-63-78
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item211.
  - On Our Way: A Women's Newspaper, 1972 - 1973; F-111-8-0-0-64 (Urc tote box 111-23)
  - Open Road, 1976 - 1981; F-111-8-0-0-65 (Urc tote box 111-23)
  - The Optimist, 1979 - 1980; F-111-8-0-0-66 (Urc tote box 111-23)
  - The Other Woman, 1972 - 1976; F-111-8-0-0-67 (Newspaper box 111-34)
    - The Other Woman, March [197-]; F-111-8-0-0-67-1
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item212.
    - The Other Woman, vol. 1 no. 1, May 1972 - June 1972; F-111-8-0-0-67-2
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item213.
    - The Other Woman, vol. 1 no. 2, September 1972; F-111-8-0-0-67-3
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item214.
    - The Other Woman, vol. 1 no. 6, July 1973 - August 1973; F-111-8-0-0-67-4
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item215.
    - The Other Woman, vol. 2 no. 1, September 1973 - October 1973; F-111-8-0-0-67-5
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item216.
    - The Other Woman, vol. 2 no. 2, November 1973 - December 1973; F-111-8-0-0-67-6
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item217.
    - The Other Woman, vol. 2 no. 4, 1974; F-111-8-0-0-67-7
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item218.
    - The Other Woman, vol. 2 no. 5, June 1974; F-111-8-0-0-67-8
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item219.
    - The Other Woman, vol. 2 no. 6, July 1974; F-111-8-0-0-67-9
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item220.
    - The Other Woman, vol. 3 no. 1, August 1974; F-111-8-0-0-67-10
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item221.
    - The Other Woman, vol. 3 no. 2, 1974; F-111-8-0-0-67-11
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item222.
    - The Other Woman, vol. 3 no. 3, 1975; F-111-8-0-0-67-12
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item223.
    - The Other Woman, vol. 3 no. 4, 1975; F-111-8-0-0-67-13
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item224.
    - The Other Woman, vol. 3 no. 5, August 1975 - September 1975; F-111-8-0-0-67-14
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item225.
    - The Other Woman, vol. 4 no. 2, March 1976 - April 1976; F-111-8-0-0-67-15
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-111-8-0-0-63, F-111-item226.
    - The Other Woman, vol. 4 no. 3, May 1976 - June 1976; F-111-8-0-0-67-16